hi and welcome to living in Central Texas\h
I'm Andrea Dudik Realtor and Associate\h\h
broker with Vista Real Estate and today\h
I'm going to show you what $379,000 can\h\h
buy you in this Lakeside Community\h
of Tanglewood within Temple Texas
[Music]now if you're new to my Channel don't\h
forget to subscribe like this video and click\h\h
the Bell icon so you can stay up to date\h
on all things happening in real estate\h\h
within Central Texas now before we head\h
inside I'll tell you a little bit about\h\h
the property this is a four bed two\h
bath home just over 1,800 Square ft\h\h
built in 2020 the community is fantastic\h
it has a community pool Community Park
and a walking trail down to the lake so\h
people will go down in kayak or canoe so\h\h
lots of really cool amenities and you are super\h
close to boat and docking access if you want to\h\h
fish or do any recreational activities like\h
that and one of the best things about this\h\h
area is that there are deer everywhere this\h
home does not have a back fence and so even\h\h
as I was outside earlier I was hanging out\h
with some really awesome [Music] deer um so\h\h
without further Ado let's go see what $379,000\h
can buy you in this awesome area let's take a
[Music]
look so we are at 15902 Solado\h
Drive Temple Texas welcome inside\h\h
I think we picked the absolute\h
perfect time to tour this home\h\h
it is so beautiful and sunny outside\h
probably around 70° and we are in mid
October I'm a really big fan of this two-toned\h
cabinets in the kitchen blue on the island and\h\h
then your white on the other cabinets granite\h
countertops and glass tile backsplash stainless\h\h
steel dish washer stove and microwave the\h
fridge does come with in this property we\h\h
have an oversized Pantry the living space is\h
super open to the dining space and kitchen the\h\h
laundry room with built-in cabinets is just\h
off of the kitchen and dining space connected\h\h
to the garage as we step into the master\h
bedroom we have recess lighting and a fan\h\h
it is all also very bright in here what's really\h
great about this property is you can see trees\h\h
from every window in the living space you can\h
see trees in the backyard in the dining space\h\h
you can see trees it's just feels you feel\h
very connected with nature and it's really\h\h
beautiful out here luxury vinyl plank in all\h
of the main living spaces with carpet in the\h\h
bedrooms you have double doors that open into\h
your master bath with dual vanities [Music]
separate soaking tub and shower\h
with tile flooring throughout
and then the guest bathroom again ceramic\h\h
tile a ton of cabinet space granite\h
countertops and a shower tub combo
and uh as you can tell the home is super bright\h
tons of lighting we have recess Lighting in the\h\h
main living spaces the backyard is beautiful\h
with a covered patio and um it's not fenced in\h\h
so you're able to sit outside drink your coffee\h
and watch the deer roam around you um again it's\h\h
on a third of an acre it has a storage shed on\h
this property you could of course fence it off\h\h
if you wanted to all of the homes in this area\h
are on septic this home is part of Belton ISD\h\h
within the city of Temple so Belton is going to\h
be your school district you're about 20 minutes\h\h
from downtown Temple 45 minutes from Fort Cavazos\h
and just over an hour to Austin just under an hour\h\h
to Waco Texas if you're looking for peaceful\h
living but close enough to amenities you will\h\h
love this home well on behalf of me and my\h
many dear friend thank you for joining us\h\h
on this awesome property tour today I hope\h
that you loved it and fell in love with this\h\h
wonderful Community if you'd like any more\h
information on this community or any others\h\h
in the area you know where to find me on my\h
contact information is below talk to you soon